bethlehemmatrimonial.com 2017-06-07

# Bethlehem Matrimonial - Since 1996 - The Exclusive Kerala Christian Matrimonial Institution having Pre-marriage Counseling Free for All and Elite Kerala Christian Matrimonial Services for Roman Catholics, Syrian Catholics, Latin Catholics, Knanaya Catholics, Malankara Catholics, Chaldean, Anglo Indians, Jacobites, Marthomites, Orthodox and CSI Christians.

Bethlehem Matrimonial is an online matrimonial service website. This privacy statement covers all the services provided by Bethlehem Matrimonial. As we are committed to protect your right to privacy, we have drawn out a privacy statement with regard to the information we collect from you. In order to provide this facility, you have to acknowledge that you are disclosing information voluntarily. By using the website and/or by providing your information, you need to express your consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the website in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to use your information, please do not use or access this website.

We use a secure server for credit card transactions to protect the credit card information of our users and cookies are used to store the login information. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that will assist us in providing our services. You may also encounter cookies, or identical or related devices on certain pages of the website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

#### Information you need to provide to use this website

The information we gather from the members and visitors who apply for our various services are email address, first name, last name, date of birth, educational qualifications, a user-specified password, mailing address, pin code and telephone/mobile number.

In case you use credit card/debit card to remit the fees we charge, some additional information’s like a billing address, credit/debit card number & expiration date and tracking information from cheques or demand drafts are collected.

#### Use of information the site collects or tracks

Bethlehem Matrimonial collects information from our users primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfil your requirements and to deliver personalised experience.

#### How the site shares the information it collects or tracks

Bethlehem Matrimonial does not sell, rent or loan out any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. At the same time, we could share such identifiable information with our associates, affiliates or subsidiaries and such associates, affiliates or subsidiaries could market to you as a result of such sharing. Any information you give us is held with utmost care and security. We are also bound to cooperate fully, when a situation arises where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer or a visitor.

Our website links to other websites that could collect personally identifiable information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy policy or the contents of those linked websites.

#### No payment for visitors

There is no payment involved in visiting our website. All visitors to our site could browse the site, search the ads and view any articles or features our site has to offer without sharing any personal information or paying any money.

#### Change of Privacy Policy

We could change this Privacy Policy without notice from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company.

#### For grievances, please contact:

Mr George Kadankavil   
The Grievance officer   
Bethlehem Matrimonial   
Behind St Anthony’s Church   
Kaloor, Kochi, Kerala 682017

The Grievance Officer will be available between 10 am to 6 pm IST from Monday to Saturday, excluding Public Holidays in India. The Grievance officer is appointed as per Section 5 (9) of the Information Technology (Reasonable Security & Procedures and Sensitive Personal data or Information) Rule, 2011.
